vincecamuto.com 2018-03-28

# Privacy Policy

## VINCECAMUTO.COM WEBSITE PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for your interest in the VinceCamuto.com website ("VC Website). This Privacy Policy describes what personally-identifiable and non-personal information we collect from you through your use of this website , including any email submissions you send to this website, and how we may use and/or disclose such information to third parties. This Policy also covers how the VC Website handles the security and management of your information, phishing concerns, use of cookies, changes in website ownership and use of the VC Website by children. You must consent to this Policy and you agree that your use of the VC Website evidences such consent. Please read this Privacy Policy before using the Website or before submitting any personal information. This Privacy Policy does not cover your use of any third-party websites that are linked through hypertext to the VC Website. If you leave the VC Website to use any of those or other third-party websites, please refer to their individual privacy policies before using such third-party website. By using this Website, you agree to the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personally-identifiable and non-personal information. You are encouraged to view the VC Website Privacy Policy whenever you access the Site to view the most current version of the Privacy Policy and to understand how your information will be collected, used and/or disclosed. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy now or on future visits, please do not use the VC Website.

THE COLLECTION, USE, AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION

**What is Personally-Identifiable Information?**

Personally-Identifiable Information may include your name, personal email address, billing address, zip code, payment information , date of birth (excluding year), and other personal information concerning your interests, preferences, occupation, gender and other demographic information; and other such information.

**What is Non-Personal Information?**

Non-Personal Information is that information which may be collected from you through your use of the VC Website, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address and the domain names from which you accessed the VC Website and to which you go after leaving the VC Website. In addition, we may collect information about your browsing preferences and habits, such as the dates and times when you visit the VC Website, the areas or pages of the Site that you visit, the amount of time you spend visiting the Site, the number of times you visit the Site and other "clickstream" data. We may combine the information we collect from you with information we receive from other online and offline sources.

**Use and/or Disclosure of Your Information**

The VC Website uses your personally-identifiable information to customize your experience in using the Site and to customize offers, advertising, specials, new product information and other VC Website news or content that we send or present to you either directly or through our marketing partners and other affiliates. In addition, the VC Website uses your personally-identifiable information to complete any purchase or service requests you make and to communicate as may be necessary with you about such purchases or requested services or, in general, concerning your use of the Site. Your personally-identifiable information may also be used to review and monitor the usage of the VC Website and operations, to enhance and protect the security or integrity of the VC Website and e-commerce business, and/or to address and remedy any problems with the VC Website, the e-commerce business or any of the products and services offered through this Site.

We may transfer or otherwise disclose information collected from and about you, both non-personal and personally-identifiable, to the following entities only for the following purposes: (i) to employees, independent contractors, consultants, business associates, service providers and suppliers and any other entities involved with the maintenance and operation of the VC Website where the disclosure of your information will enable these entities to perform business, professional or technical supporting functions for the VC Website; (ii) to employees, independent contractors, service providers and suppliers where such disclosure enables the fulfillment of your product or service request; (iii) as necessary if we believe that you have violated or are under investigation for a potential violation of the VC Website Terms and Conditions of Use or of the rights of any of the entities involved with supporting the VC Website or any rights of any third party; (iv) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or as otherwise required by law; (v) to investigate the threat of potential fraud or to investigate suspected or actual fraud involving user use of the VC Website or other such related conduct; and/or (vi) as provided for elsewhere within this Policy.

Furthermore, the VC Website may share with or provide access to third-parties and affiliates your personally-identifiable and non-personally-identifiable information where we believe you would benefit from receiving contact from that party. The VC Website will not share any of your personally-identifiable financial information with any third-party or affiliate that is not otherwise privy to such information as previously described within this Privacy Policy.

**SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION**

The VC Website relies on the use of reasonable physical, electronic, contractual and managerial measures to safeguard and maintain all personally-identifiable information provided by you through the VC Website on computer servers in a controlled and secured environment in an effort to restrict and impair unauthorized access, loss, alteration, use or disclosure of such information. However, the nature of the Internet is such that information may be transmitted over networks without appropriate security measures and may be accessed, deleted, altered, used or disclosed by unauthorized persons.

Because of the world-wide nature of the services and products provided by this Website and the nature of the business supporting Vince Camuto, LLC d/b/a Camuto Group, personal data may, subject to applicable laws, be transferred internationally amongst the entities responsible for creating and selling the Camuto Group lines, for the purposes described above. This may result in personal data being transferred to countries which do not have laws or regulations protecting personal data, such as the United States. We use reasonable measures to limit the disclosure and processing of the data you provide to us only to certain staff within our operating entities and our affiliates, namely those staff members, contractors and affiliates who must process your inquiries and other customer services requests or those who are responsible for administering the VC Website.

The VC Website also takes precautions to keep your personally-identifiable financial information private and safe. The VC Website relies on current, industry-standard technology to encrypt your order information and to process your credit card information in a secure area of the site. Although the VC Website uses its best efforts to take such precautions with your personally-identifiable financial information, you understand and acknowledge through your use of this Site that no transmission of data over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted and/or misused by third parties.

**PHISHING**

"Phishing" refers to the attempt by a third-party to criminally and fraudulently acquire sensitive information such as user names, passwords and credit card details from Internet users, by masquerading as a trustworthy entity, and is a type of Internet scam that is becoming increasingly common and pervasive. To avoid being a victim of this scam, be wary of emails that you receive from what appear to be legitimate sources, such as the VC Website, seeking to collect your personally-identifiable information through such means as a hypertext link incorporated in such email. If the VC Website needs to verify your personally-identifiable information in order to process an order request or a service request submitted by you, such verification will not be done through an email incorporating these hypertext links. If you do encounter this type of email or are suspicious that any email you allegedly receive from the VC Website is fraudulent, please forward the email to the VC Website at [customerservice@VinceCamuto.com](mailto:customerservice@VinceCamuto.com) and contact Customer Service directly. We will investigate all instances of possible Internet fraud.

**MANAGEMENT OF YOUR INFORMATION**

You are entitled to request access to and correction of all your personally-identifiable information and data as collected by us through the VC Website. You can make this request or a related inquiry by emailing us or by otherwise contacting us as noted elsewhere on the Site. Please note that there may be a processing fee involved, depending on the circumstances relating to your inquiry and/or request. You may choose not to receive unsolicited marketing material from the VC Website (opt-out) and you have the right to request deletion of your account information, subject to the Website�s need to maintain appropriate archives of its business operations. Please note that a decision to opt-out of receiving unsolicited marketing material from the VC Website may not stop advertising or content that is generated prior to the time when we can accomplish the removal of your information from the Site records.

**OUR USE OF COOKIES AND SPYWARE**

We never use or install spyware on your computer nor do we use spyware to retieve information from your computer

Cookies are small text files that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access any website, including the VC Website. The VC Website relies on the use of Cookies and may rely on the use of other tracking technology to augment the interactivity of your experience with the VC Website and to make your future visits to the VC Website more enjoyable and convenient. The use of cookies allows the VC Website to monitor your use of the Site and to access information saved from your prior visits to the Site about features you may have selected to customize your use of the VC Website and to provide you with customized advertising offers. Please note that personally-identifiable information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally-identifiable information to the VC Website, cookies may be linked or tied to such information. This aggregate cookie and/or tracking information may be shared with third-parties.

You are free to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features, including promotional offers, of the VC Website. Check the Help menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

USE OF THE WEBSITE BY CHILDREN The VC Website is not meant for children and, as such, does not seek to collect personally-identifiable information from children, defined as those persons under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personally-identifiable information to us. If you are the parent or guardian of a person under the age of 13 who has provided such personally-identifiable information to us, please inform us through the VC Website or any listed contact means, such as telephone, and we will remove such personally-identifiable information from our Site records as described in this Privacy Policy.

**THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES AND HYPERTEXT LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES**

The VC Website may contain hypertext links to third-party websites that may or may not be created or maintained by the same parties who control the VC Website. This Privacy Policy applies to only this website and you should refer to the individual policies of any third-party websites that you visit through hypertext links hosted on the VC Website. The VC Website is not responsible for the content of the third-party privacy policies, including the accuracy or completeness of such content. The inclusion of any hypertext link on the VC Website does not imply endorsement of, sponsorship by, affiliation with, or recommendation for any hypertext-linked third-party website by the VC Website. The VC Website disclaims any liability for links (i) from another website to the VC Website and (ii) to another website from the VC Website. The VC Website cannot guarantee the standards of any third-party website to which links are provided on the VC Website and it shall not be held responsible for the contents of such third-party websites, including other hypertext links, webcasting, streaming or any other transmission, whether hosted on such third-party website or received by the VC Website from any linked website. For these reasons, VC Website does not represent or warrant that the contents of any third-party website are accurate, compliant with applicable laws, including state, federal, copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. VC Website does not endorse the contents of any third-party website in any way. Any reliance on the contents of a third-party website is done at your own risk and you assume all responsibilities and consequences resulting from such reliance.

**BUSINESS ACQUISITIONS OR TRANSACTIONS INVOLVING THE OWNERSHIP OR MANAGEMENT OF THE VINCECAMUTO WEBSITE**

The parties responsible for bringing the Jessica Simpson Collection to you through the VC Website may be sold in part or may otherwise change ownership or control. In addition, these parties may acquire additional other businesses or entities. In such transactions, your personally-identifiable and non-personally-identifiable information may be disclosed to third-parties or may be one of the transferred business assets.

**CONSENT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY**

You acknowledge that the VC Website Privacy Policy is part of the terms of service for the VC Website and you agree that your use of this Site signifies your acceptance of such Privacy Policy terms as now drafted or as drafted in the future.

The VC Website Privacy Policy may undergo changes, modifications, deletions or additions from time-to-time (collectively, changes). In the event that such changes to the Policy constitute material alterations concerning how the VC Website collects, processes, stores, uses and/or discloses your personally-identifiable information and non-personally-identifiable information, such changes will be noted in the revised VC Website Privacy Policy or elsewhere within the content of the VC Website and the revised Privacy Policy will be posted with an updated effective date.

**CONTACT US**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, contact us at [customerservice@VinceCamuto.com](mailto:customerservice@VinceCamuto.com)
